Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/nguyentran-trung-nguyen-b602b0162 (LinkedIn) ktsnttnguyen.wixsite.com/home (Personal)

Top Skills

Communication
Management
CPM Scheduling

Languages

Vietnamese (Native or Bilingual) English (Professional Working)

Certifications

Partipated in the master class " Danish Week - Sustainable city solution"

Certified Organization Committee of ICAPPS HCMC 2018

Certified International Summer Program in Architecture: Cities in Asia 2017

Urban planning practice Certificate

Certificate of merit is to confirm that Student had highest GPA in Urban planning at UAH 2013-2018

Honors-Awards

Highest cumulative grade-point average (GPA 3.30/4.00)

Top 5 average-point of 2018 final graduation projects (8.67/10.00)

Highest cumulative grade-point average (GPA 3.69/4.00)

Publications

Partial urban morphology CBD area in HCMc

Applicability of Contemporary
Architecture Movement to VietNam

Nguyen Tran Trung-Nguyen

M. Project manager | B. Architect Deputy Urban design manager at THE FIVE AND PARTNERS

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Summary

Experienced Management and Consultant design in Construction field. Skilled in Open Mind, Independence, Creative Problem Solving, Responsiveness, and Planning. Strong community and social services professional graduated Project management Master degree from Asian Institute of Technology, Thailand and Architectural degree from University of Architecture Ho Chi Minh city, Vietnam.

Experience

THE FIVE AND PARTNERS

7 years 7 months

Urban Planner & Project Manager September 2018 - Present (6 years 7 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

- Experienced lots of kind of urban planning (large scale, small scale, urban design, researching, cost estimates, etc) and step of urban planning project in VietNam juridically
- Getting involved in many large and medium architectural design projects, with extensive experience in developing concepts and diagrams

Urban Planner

September 2017 - November 2024 (7 years 3 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

ADEPTA STUDIO

Architect

March 2016 - November 2024 (8 years 9 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

- Interior, architecture and landscaping designs, conceptual diagram and 2D, 3D visualization
- Experienced over 10 actual projects, coordinated with other consultant, constructors and customers

The Good Line: research and applicability to Vietnam

Education

Asian Institute of Technology

Master's degree, Project Management in Construction · (August 2023 - November 2024)

University of Architecture of Ho Chi Minh City (HCMC)
Bachelor's degree, Land Use Planning and Management/
Development · (September 2013 - August 2018)